One dream.
One wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Darkstorm, there you are.
Where have you been?
Is there something wrong, Kin'emon?
There's a problem afoot.
The enemy has learned of our
fire and mark of the moon?
Afraid so.
We're into Major Hot Water now.
How can we even fix this mess, Duke?
We took such care to be safe
when we distributed them.
How in the world did
they foil us like this?
We even chose this
coded symbol and the off
chance that it fell into unintended hands.
I can't imagine how
they were able to decode
our message and learn
of the tattoo's meaning.
Where could we possibly have gone wrong?
And our problems don't end there.
There are reports that
our allies in the capital
were apprehended by Kaido
and Orochi's forces.
You're under arrest!
There's no use resisting.
We know everything.
Look what he had.
You think you're smart, huh?
Check it out.
He's got the moon tattoo.
Those who bear that mark are
considered traitors to the Shogun.
You hear?
You are to report all rebels.
Word travels fast.
Everyone in the capital
must have heard by now.
We have little to no time to
patrol the city's bathhouses.
Lucky you.
And what do you mean by that?
Only Stealth Black could
have pulled that off.
I'll get him next time.
You were there too, if I recall, so
don't pin all of that mess on me.
Sir Kyoshiro, I'm afraid that
Komorosaki's wake has been cancelled.
We feared chaos would ensue with a
crowd of this size in attendance.
It's expected that even more people will
show up for the funeral tomorrow as well.
Please take extra caution, sir.
This tragedy has caused
unrest among the people.
They may resent you for your actions.
Of course they will.
They don't get it.
Unfortunately, there was no other way.
Besides, I'm the one who suffered the
greatest loss here Where's my pity party?
Of course, sir.
I spoke to the Shogun.
The man's absolutely furious.
Can't blame him, though?
He's got this to fear.
We're supposed to be friends, aren't we?
So talk it out.
Knock it off already.
Allies keep getting caught before we even
get a chance to see our plan take flight.
It's been happening ever since
your crew compromised us.
What are you implying?
That white bear and his friends talked.
How else would the enemy
forces know of our plan, huh?
My crew would sooner die
than rat out our allies.
So watch your mouth!
Wait, this is exactly
what they want, Traffy.
Why don't you mind your
own business, Blackleg?
I'll make the call.
Slow down and cool your heads, you guys.
I don't think my head is the one you
should be worrying about right now.
In times like these, it's
important to trust your friends.
Are you serious?
You're the least
trustworthy person I know!
I, uh, didn't see anything.
That's the most jacked
up face I've ever seen.
It's what you get, I guess.
Just where are you going?
You must sever ties with
those who were captured
Your friends are dead to
us now What'd you say?
A ninja knows when to cut their
losses You're scaring me, Shinobu!
This isn't some child's game we're
playing here, you know It's been so long.
This is it.
We have waited 20 years for this.
If we fail this time, there
will be no second chances.
Control yourself, Shinobu.
I'm sorry, Master Khan.
Things will not always go as we had hoped.
I understand your frustration,
but without the help of these people whose
goals miraculously align with our own,
we'd be nowhere.
We must all work together.
Fulfill Lord Odin's wish.
Hello!
Party's here!
I couldn't help but overhear
you from outside the window.
And oh boy, you folks have
some nice pipes, I tell ya.
Hang on a sec.
Who even are you?
Oh, wow, what a beauty.
Are you some kind of goddess?
Aw, aren't you sweet? Come on in.
Well, don't mind if I do. Thank you.
I know you, Yoshinobu.
Yes, and you, Kanjuro, right?
Would you look at that?
Seems like you're the real deal.
I'm relieved, as I got an invite to a
special event, if you catch my drift.
This is all the rage
in the capital, I hear.
I'm getting a little
starstruck, truth be told.
So lay it on me, chief.
Is there a big battle of Bruin?
That's my sword.
My sword!
Wait a sec.
You really scared me!
Please, we need to rest.
We don't want that wound opening up.
You gotta listen to it and go back to bed!
Where am I?
If it weren't for your assistance, I fear
that we might have died earlier today.
You have my gratitude.
Thanks a bunch, mister!
You suffered a terrible
wound on our behalf.
I'm sorry.
I hope I can make it up to you somehow.
No, it was my own fault
that I got hurt like this.
You two had nothing to do with any of it.
I gotta find that guy.
Where the hell did he go?
That jackass still has my shoes wet! No!
If you don't stay and
recover, you could die!
Ah, come on!
That's the shoulder that got
stabbed, you freakin' idiot!
My apologies! I'm leaving!
Don't try to stop me!
Stay a bit longer?
just until the pain goes away.
Ugh, you're the one who's causing my pain!
What is wrong with you?
I-I'm so sorry!
You'll be okay, and I can help!
Do you know how?
Back in the capital, there
was this toad oil I stole.
I mean, that I bought!
Jess said you stole it.
No, I paid for it, silly!
Whatever, I don't care.
Watch what it can do.
It makes all the sword boo-boos go away.
Does it really now?
Okay, let's hope this works.
But I think...
You should stay.
That food over there?
Oh, yes.
Allow me to serve you.
Who's this Gyukimaru? Ah, yes.
The man's a well-known figure.
He stands guard on Bandit's bridge.
I have reclaimed Shusui and returned
it to the only place that it belongs.
That fabed sword is a
national treasure that was
taken from the grave of the
legendary samurai, Ryuma!
No one knows who he is
or from whence he hails,
But whenever anyone carrying a
weapon attempts to cross that bridge,
then you can be certain
that he will appear.
So there's no need to
rush back and fight him.
I'll go deal with him later.
Well, I'm curious to
know more about the guy.
I guess first I should learn more
about who's right in front of me.
Who are you and why was
that Grim Reaper after you?
In truth, we did something that
earned us the wrath of one Oshogun.
Oshogun, huh?
That, uh, Orochi guy? Orochi.
Say, Mr. Samurai!
My name is Dock!
But when you put an O in front like other
girls' names, it sounds like I'm a boy!
Isn't that so funny?
Nope. Not really.
But everyone laughs a lot when
I tell them, now why not you?
Because it's not funny.
I assumed from the way you dressed
that you were a samurai of Wano.
But it would seem you're from overseas.
You don't look like a bad person.
You look very, uh, friendly. Liar!
I'm sorry.
On the outside, you look scary.
But I know you're nice because you
saved our butts when we were in trouble!
Mr.
Samurai, I'm going to tell you
something that must remain a secret.
What is it?
I'm searching for my older brother.
We were separated 20 long years ago.
Also, I believe he may be
here in Wano right now.
My brother's name is Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'm his younger sister.
And my name is Hyori.
Momonosuke?
You're his sister?
Wait, you know him?
So my leap of faith
paid off, how wonderful!
Honestly, it was a big leap.
You've met my brother before, haven't you?
That must mean he's still alive
Oh, hold on a sec.
I need to process this.
You know, I heard there's a movement
to bring back the Kozuki clan.
Is that true?
Are you part of it? I knew it!
You're a friend of the
cause from a foreign land!
You're here to help my
brother, aren't you?
No!
Wait, you're not?
Then who are you?
A foe?
I'm an ally.
I can tell you that much.
Well, that's a relief.
What about the others, then?
Do you know if Kin'emon is still alive?
And Kanjuro, Raizo, what of Kikunojo?
Are they with you as well?
Kikunojo?
Oh, you mean Kiku, right?
Yeah, one thing, though.
I need some kind of proof.
How do I know you're really Momo's sister?
Allow me to explain.
Yeah, okay.
Guess it all adds up then?
Momo traveled two decades ahead in time.
So he's still eight years old.
And even though you're his younger sister.
You're 26 now since
you had to stay behind.
Yes.
By the way?
Are you sure this twerp's
allowed to hear all this?
Yeah, it's okay.
I already knew about it.
She told me a long time ago.
It was a special secret
between the two of us.
Otoko is one of my closest friends.
Her smiling face has gotten
me through so many hard days.
She reminds me of myself 20 years ago.
I was about her age on that day.
The day my whole world fell apart.
I'll never forget it.
Leave to the future.
Live on.
Please, I made up my mind, too!
Mother! Father!
No, I won't leave you!
At the time, I had no understanding
of what was occurring.
Suddenly, right before my eyes,
My beloved brother and the others
all vanished into the flames.
Before I could even process the death
of my father, I lost my mother as well.
Everything was taken
from me in a single day.
I was told that my brother
would return in twenty years.
But after a tragedy so great, such an
immaterial hope offered me little solace.
I completely lost the will to go on.
Why didn't they have you jump
into the future with your brother?
It was either him or me.
We couldn't let the Kozuki bloodline die.
If something happened to both
of us, then all would be lost.
So that's why.
That's messed up.
I was never completely alone, though.
My father's ally,
a kindly retainer named Kawamatsu the
Kappa, raised me with patience and care.
A Kappa? Indeed.
Hard to believe that he's
one of those river creatures,
but he's not ashamed of that fact.
He takes pride in it.
The day that the castle burned
down, we were surrounded by enemies.
However, he helped me escape
through the moat undetected.
Princess, just a bit longer.
After losing my father, mother,
and brother, the shock robbed
me of my ability to speak.
but he did his utmost best to cheer me up.
Princess, this is the cup-a-dance.
Surprise, I brought you food. Dig in.
Your tummy is saying it's
hungry, too, isn't it?
No, I have a bit of an
upset stomach, you see.
That's why it's being so noisy.
That's a fib.
Can't you at least put
half of this with me?
No, no, it's fine.
I found a grilled fish
swimming in the river earlier.
A grilled fish was in
the water? Yes, indeed.
I filleted and gobbled up
that tasty little fellow.
So don't you worry about me, all right?
He would always make sure to feed me,
even if that meant there
was nothing left for him.
I owe everything to him.
His kindness allowed
me to smile once more.
If it weren't for his help,
I'd have been lost to sorrow.
So where is he now?
When I was about 13, we were separated.
Since then, I haven't seen him.
However, he is a samurai.
Kawamatsu must be out there somewhere.
I know it!
Certainly he's waiting for the day of
the great battle to make his return.
How I wish to see him again,
as well as the others.
I've never met a real Cape before!
Sir Zorojuro? Hmm?
If I may ask you, who's here to
help prepare for the big uprising?
There's a few of us.
What? What?
So the doggie and the kitty
are with you as well? Yeah.
But I had heard that they were both dead.
I was certain I would
never see them again.
I don't think Cat Vipers arrived here
yet, but he's involved in the plans.
What's with that face?
I am just so happy.
I can't cry now I am a samurai's daughter
considering that the
doggy and kitty made it
back all of the Akazaya
9 could reunite that
would be like a dream
well don't get your hopes
There's Kin'emon,
then Kanjuro, Raizo, Okiku,
Dogstorm, and Cat Viper.
Those are the six we have contact
with, plus Momonosuke, obviously.
But I've never even met the other
three, so who knows where they are.
One of them is Kawamatsu,
whom I just told you about.
The last three are him,
Denjiro, and Ashura Doji.
While I certainly do not know
where they are currently,
I pray that they are alive and well.
But the entire flower capital is in
an uproar over this symbolic flyer.
I am certain they know and will appear.
Those are the flyers we handed
out to the rebels earlier, right?
Yes, they are.
Thanks to all this commotion,
I'm sure the word has gotten out to
just about everyone you could imagine.
But that's not exactly ideal for us.
Now the whole world
knows our meeting place,
and with all the arrests,
we're down a few men, too.
That's looking pretty dicey.
Everything will be all right.
I have absolute faith.
Well...
Too many men at the helm
always sinks the ship.
I'm not going to sit here and
sweat the details. Exactly.
We need you to relax so you can heal.
Besides, it's out of your hands.
Now get some rest.
All right.
No need to tell me twice!
Otoko, can you believe it?
My brother is alive.
Such good news.
This is great.
I'm so happy for you.
This is the best day ever.
It really is.
With all of this racket, I'm
never going to get to sleep.
He's eight years old.
Hard to believe.
To think he's still but a child.
They'll all be just as I remember
them from two decades ago.
I wonder what will happen once I see
them all again, but that's selfish.
I should wait till the battle's won.
I don't wish to distract. That's right.
I should be patient.
Don't you think?
I wouldn't have thought there were
so many conspirators amongst us.
All who are present, bear
witness to these traitors.
These are the faces of
those who dare to take a
stand against Shogun
Orochi and Commander Kaido.
Stop stalling!
I do sympathize.
You've been plotting this for
quite some time, haven't you?
And you failed.
Fukurokuju, sir, please don't do this!
We're all innocent.
Why do you think these ankle tattoos
are a sign that we're criminals?
This is but a popular design.
We have nothing to do with any rebellion.
Is that so?
Well, then, I challenge you to
explain the meaning of this flyer.
The implication is quite clear.
Why else would there be a reversed
crescent moon at the center?
No matter how you look at it, it spells
out insurrection against Shogun Oroji.
It undoubtedly resembles your tattoos.
You've caused enough trouble.
Now accept your punishment.
They're in some deep crap, huh?
I hope nobody thinks we talked.
They know we would never
rat them out, don't they?
Don't worry, you guys.
No matter what, Captain
Law will have our backs.
Show us what else you got!
I could go for a bit of sumo myself.
The name's Medilloman.
I'm a mess you up.
I'm a gift or tell.
Ah!
Your body looks pretty tough.
That I can work with.
You think this is fun?
These are loaded with
C-prism stone bullets.
You won't be smiling for long.
Come on and try me!
That's over for you!
It's over, he says.
This thing isn't over, not by a long shot.
Keep it up.
Oh, man, head to the right,
duck, and then jump up.
Go to hell!
Now! Sure!
Ah!
Get done!
As instructed. Daniel! Then jump!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Nice, old man!
You pulled it off! What the?
Are you able to see the future?
That's amazing!
That does it!
Look, I don't know what
trick you just pulled,
but I'm done screwing around with you!
Old man, head to the left! Huh?
You're gonna die!
Ha-ha!
If you say so!
Tricky old fart!
How do you like this?
Stop moving!
You're playing in my ass!
You're dead!
You'll need to try a little harder.
Ah, fine!
How about this?
All right, then.
Let's roll!
No contact! Right!
Ah!
All right, then. Let's roll!
Oh, man.
That was just normal armament Haki.
Crap.
Arm-a-day fire!
That's not it.
I still can't figure out
how I'm messing this up.
Huh?
Where'd you go to hit me?
Alpaca Fancy!
Hey!
Which way should I go next?
You listening, Mr. Straw Hat?
Uh-huh, stop right there!
Hold tight, it'll be easier this way.
I'm so sorry.
Let's do this thing, I'll pack a man!
Oh, yeah, leave it to me.
Put me down!
I already feel awful over
how much trouble I've caused.
Nah, I think the heavier I
am, the better, actually.
Huh?
It'll help with my training.
You guys are really something.
I must admit, this was a brilliant idea.
Crystal clear and straight to the point.
Even a fool like me could tell
what the two flaming birds meant.
It's going down the day of
the fire festival at twilight.
Then the meetin' place is Habu Port.
Man, I gotta say, Kinama did good.
How do you know him?
Speak up.
Aw, what's with the long face, Shinobu?
Cheer up, my dear.
Well, I guess I really can't blame you.
I'd be pretty glum myself in your shoes.
The plan is coming apart at the seams.
And the bad guys are in the know.
Indeed quite regrettable, it is.
It also grieves me to know
that our comrades bearing
the tattoo have been
apprehended on our account.
Ah, if only you could
claim it was all a lie,
but then you'd mislead
your allies too well done.
We're in quite the pickle here, aren't we?
It's such a shame, I.
I wish I'd known about
those ankle tattoos sooner.
But tattoo or no, folks are watching.
Ah, still no good.
I can't figure this thing out.
Huh?
They went flying.
Did you not want that?
it's not that simple old man i want to
throw a punch and knock them back but do it
without contact i gotta
learn i have a feeling
that's what it's gonna
take to break through
kaido's tough scales you want to send people
flying without touching them yeah i've
seen it done before by
two people but i can't
figure out how it works first was railing
the second was by a
battle axe guy they were
using armament Haki why can't i do it like
they did Haki must be
the foreign terminology
for it hang on you know it an invisible
power from within the body we have something
like that here in wano you can use it
with a blade too strongly
enough to cut iron
or Gently enough to leave paper unharmed.
It's entirely up to the wielder.
Hmm?
Ugh.
Oh, man!
Got a death wish or something
getting this close to me?
Watch, Mr. Straw Hat.
I will now demonstrate the
technique I was referring to.
It's been a while.
So even though he's a prisoner
stuck in this sick execution game,
he's still working on making
himself even stronger?
Is he nuts?
Just like before, give me directions!
OK!
The fluffy guy is gonna use
his right hand to swing! Ah!
Sounds good to me.
Ah!
You think you can hit me, Grandpa?
Yeah! Ha!
That was the move!
Damn, old guy!
Old Man Yo took down a gifter!
Old Peak Man, get up!
I gotta say, I'm a little surprised.
Thought the old coot would already
have one foot in the grave.
He's still got some pep!
What the hell?
It can't be!
He's been Hyogoro the flower all along?
Well, Mr. Straw Hat?
Was that what you were attempting to do?
Something like that attack?
If so, then maybe I
can help you after all.
You really did it.
Can you teach me?
You